Athletics, Department of; Records ua746
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administrative Records, 1960-1977; 1950-2004; 2; 3 cubic ft.
  - SUNYAC Finances, 1970-1974 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - SUNYAC Tournaments, 1970-1974 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - SUNYAC Awards, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - SUNYAC Constitution, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - SUNYAC EXEC. Committee, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - SUNYAC Annual Meeting State University of New York at Albany Athletics Conference, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - SUNYAC Publicist-Coach Accolades, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Visiting Groups: Summer Session, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Swimming Coach Evaluation, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Team Captains, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Team Records and All Time Scoring Leaders, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Team Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Team Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Team Rosters, 1952-1968 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Team Rosters, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Team Rosters, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Team Rosters, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Team Rosters, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Team Rosters, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Transportation, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Transportation, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Varsity Athletics Contracts: Analysis, 1950-1967 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Varsity Athletics Clippings, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Varsity Soccer: Albany - Montclair Game Report on, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Varsity Soccer "All- America" Nominees, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Varsity Soccer: Approved Soccer Officials, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Varsity Soccer Clinics: A Study Guide for (Joseph Garcia's Master Thesis), Undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Varsity Soccer: Clippings + Photos, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Varsity Soccer Conferences: NSCA "All America", 1950-1958 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Varsity Soccer Conferences: NYSIAC, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Varsity Soccer Conferences: SUNYAC "All-Star", 1963 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Varsity Soccer Conferences: National Soccer Coaches Association of America " All N.Y.S." ( NSCAA), 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Varsity Soccer Conference: ECAC Awards Committee, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Varsity Soccer: Dance + Coordination, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Varsity Soccer: Soccer Manual, Undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Varsity Soccer: Pre-Season Mailing, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Varsity Soccer Scheduled Absences, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Varsity Sports Bulletin, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Varsity Wrestling Championships + Tournaments, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Varsity Wrestling: Clippings, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Wrestling Photographs, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Wrestling Publicity, 1971-1974 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Varsity Wrestling Post-Season Tournaments Request, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Varsity Wrestling Pre-Season Practice: Letters, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Varsity Wrestling SUNYA Wrestling Clinics, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Varsity Wrestling: Survey + Technique, Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Warren W. Crow (Wrestling) (Resumee), Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Women's Sports Reports, 1966-1970 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Annual Report (Women's Intercollegiate Athletics), 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Annual Report (WAA) includes WAA Constitution (4/26/68), 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Women's Intercollegiate Report, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Annual Report, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Women's Budget, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - NYS Association of Intercollegiate Athletics for Women, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Women's Varsity Sports Organization of New York State Colleges (WVSONYSC) (I), 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Sports Crew Men/Women, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - WVSONYSC (II), 1964-1972 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Won-Lost by Season, Undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - NY Senate Proclamation for Bobford Retirement, ca. 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - State of New York Legislature, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Athletic Advisory Board, 1952-1977; 3; 0.66 cubic ft.
  Contains predominantly minutes of the Athletic Advisory Board (A.A. Board) from 1955 to 1976, maintained by the Director of Athletics in his function as Secretary of the Board, as well as supporting budgets, correspondence, memoranda, and scattered A.A. Board reports, 1952, 1955-1976.
  Correspondents include Dr. Alfred Werner, Director of Athletics, and Joseph Garcia, Coordinator of Varsity Athletics, as well as the coaching staff. Also contained in the records are of the Athletics, and the Final Report of the University Athletics Council in regarding to the inter-collegiate sports (May 1968).
  Also included are lists of sports rosters, and the outstanding athletics who received awards at the Annual AA Board "All Sports Banquet."
  - Criteria for Intercollegiate Activities, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Athletic Awards-Correspondence, 1969; 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - A.A. Bd. All Sports Banquet includes sport results, outstanding teams, most improved players, 1970 May 20 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - A.A. Board Minutes and Proposals, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - AA Board Minutes, Proposals and Memoranda, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Information includes correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - A.A. Board Minutes, Memoranda and Miscellaneous, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - A.A. Board Finance Policy, 1973 March (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - A.A. Board Minutes, Proposals and Memoranda, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - A.A. Board Minutes, Memoranda and Miscellaneous, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - A.A. Board Minutes, Memoranda and Miscellaneous includes proposal for volleyball for men and woman becomes athletic Finance Committee, Nov. 1975, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - AFC Proposals, Memoranda, Miscellaneous, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - A.A. BD: Objectives of the Intercollegiate Athletic Program, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Semi-Annual Report of The State College AAB, 1952 October (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - AAB Compiled Minutes, 1955-1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - A.A. Board Minutes includes (12/3/64) document about incorporation of football as a variety sport at university, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - A.A. Board Minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Rf. Control of Intercollegiate Athletics Report to Vice President of Student Affairs, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - A.A. Banquet, 1966 May 24; 1967 March 21 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - A.A. Board Minutes and Memoranda, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - A.A. Board- All Sports Banquet, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - A.A. Board Minutes Memos and Proposal, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Final Report of the University Athletics Council, 1968 May (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - All Sports Banquet, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - A.A. Board Minutes, Proposals and Miscellaneous, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - A.A. Board Report to Central Council RE: Budget- General Statements, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Constitution Women's Varsity Sports Organization of N.Y.S, 1969 January 15 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - All Sports Banquet, 1969 May 22 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - A.A. Board Minutes and Memorands, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Team Rosters and Season Summaries, 6.49 cubic ft.
  This series is divided into two sub-series for men's athletics and women's athletics. The Athletics department maintained each series separately, with each year in a large binder.
  This series is useful for finding cursory sports team information, with files including team rosters and schedules with some including game results or statistics for the individual sport as well. These files contain basic information for men's and women's athletic teams each academic year spanning from the 1992-1993 season to the 2008-2009 season. The records were originally maintained in binders by the Athletic Department according to men's sports and women's sports for each year available. Not every year includes files for every sport. Collective yearly athletics schedules are occasionally included. In some instances, personally identifiable information and/or sensitive material was redacted to protect the security of individuals mentioned.
  - Men's Team Rosters and Season Summaries, 2.83 cubic ft.
    The files are arranged in their original order by season. The files are arranged by date of content listed in the title field, not by creation date. Within each season, the files are arranged alphabetically.
    - Season Baseball, 1992-1993; 1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Season Basketball, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Season Cross Country, 1992-1993; 1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Season Soccer, 1992-1993; 1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Season Tennis, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Season Athletic Schedules, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Season Baseball, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Season Cross Country, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Season Lacrosse, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Season Football, 1993-1994; 1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Indoor Track and Field, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Season Lacrosse, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Season Soccer, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Season Swimming, 1994 January 29; 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Season Tennis, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Season Winter Games Scores, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Season Wrestling, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Albany Athletics, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Season Baseball, 1994-1995; 1995 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Season Basketball, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Season Cross Country, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Season Football Roster, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Season Lacrosse, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Season Tennis, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Track, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Season Soccer, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Season Swimming, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Season Wrestling, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Season Schedules, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Season Baseball, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Season Cross Country, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Season Indoor Track, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Season Lacrosse, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Season Outdoor Track, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Season Soccer, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Season Baseball, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Season Cross Country, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Season Indoor Track and Field, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Season Cross Country, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Season Lacrosse, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Season Outdoor Track, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Season Lacrosse, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Season Soccer, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Season Athletic Schedule, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Season Baseball, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Season Cross Country, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Season Indoor Track, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Season Lacrosse, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Season Outdoor Track, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Season Soccer, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Season Baseball, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Season Cross Country, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Season Indoor Track, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Season Lacrosse, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Season Outdoor Track, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Season Soccer, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Season Baseball, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Season Cross Country, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Season Indoor Track, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Season Lacrosse, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Season Outdoor Track, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Season Soccer, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Season Baseball, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Season Cross Country, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Season Indoor Track, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Season Lacrosse, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Season Outdoor Track, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Season Soccer, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Season Baseball, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Season Cross Country, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Season Indoor track, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Season Lacrosse, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Season Outdoor Track, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Season Soccer, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Season Baseball, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Season Cross Country, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Season Indoor Track, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Season Lacrosse, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Season Outdoor Track, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Season Soccer, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Season Baseball, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Season Cross Country, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Season Indoor Track, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Season Lacrosse, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Season Outdoor Track, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Season Soccer, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Season Baseball, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Season Cross Country, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Season Lacrosse, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Season Soccer, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Season Track and Field, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Season Baseball, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Season Cross Country, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Season Indoor Track, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Season Lacrosse, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Season Outdoor Track, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Season Soccer, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Season Baseball, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Season Cross Country, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Season Indoor Track, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Season Lacrosse, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Season Outdoor Track, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Season Soccer, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Season Baseball, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Season Cross Country, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Season Indoor Track, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Season Lacrosse, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Season Outdoor Track, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Season Soccer, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Women's Team Rosters and Season Summaries, 3.66 cubic ft.
- Men's and Women's Sports Files, 18.6 cubic ft.
  This series covers detailed files previously maintained by the University at Albany Athletics Department related to men's and women's sports that include schedules, game scores and results, statistics, correspondence, records, articles, rosters, tournament information, itineraries, individual game files, game programs, reports, budget information, memoranda, scorebooks, sports guides, and news. Specific files may encompass the records of a team's whole season, part of a season, an individual gameday, or be player-specific. Early records in the series were retained by the Director of Athletics Alfred Werner, and Coordinator/Associate Director/Director Joe Garcia. Later records were retained by Sports Information Director Brian DePasquale. In some instances, personally identifiable information and/or sensitive material was redacted to protect the security of individuals mentioned.
  This series is divided into 17 sub-series arranged alphabetically. Each sub-series is arranged chronologically.
  - Athletics Department, 0.6 cubic ft.
    This sub-series contains files that pertain to the Athletics Department of UAlbany as a whole, including: award ceremony and hall of fame programs; program-wide rosters, reports, records, and game notes; staff member files; fundraiser information; calendars and programs; recruitment initiatives; and department handbooks and directories.
    - Club Sports Flyer, 1968 Spring (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Women's Rosters, 1969-1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Women's Sports Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Women's Sports Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Women's Sports Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Women's Sports Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Women's Sports Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Hall of Fame, 1984; 1989; 1991-1992; 1994-1997; Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Fall Sports Schedule, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Records and Statistics Across Sports, 1950-2000; 1992-1998; ca. 2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - New York City: Milt Richards, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Athletics Fees, 1994 November (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Bob Beyer Reception, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Hall of Fame Guests, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - President's Recognition Dinner, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Athletic Brochure, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Athletics NYC event, 1995; 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Road Race, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Game Notes, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Lake Placid Masters World Cup, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Calendars Athletics, 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Doc Saves Dinner, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Doc Saves Retirement, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Milt Richards, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Sports Game Programs, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Party For a Plate, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Men's & Women's Recruiting Brochures and Sports Rosters, 1997-1998; 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Milt Richards Funding, 1997; Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - School of Business Kick off Reception, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Homecoming Weekends, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - University at Albany Department of Athletics and Recreation Handbook, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Scholar Athletes, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Great Dane Awards, 2001 May 5 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Ualbany Policies and Procedures Manual and Student Athlete Handbook, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Incoming Athlete Recruits, 2002 Fall (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Athletic Logo, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Collegiate Records, 1969; 2005 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - University at Albany Recruiting Policy, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Chancellor's Scholar-Athletic Award Nominations, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Meetings, Correspondence, Information, 2008; 2011-2012 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Participation Lists, 2012-2013 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Great Dane Awards, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Participation Lists, 2012-2013 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - NCAA Radio Broadcast Agreement, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Champions of Character Awards Banquet, 2014 April (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Athletics Hall of Fame Induction Ceremony, 2014 September 27 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Albany Stickers and Logos, Undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Athletics Information, Undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Athletic Logos, Undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Athletic Telephone Directory, Undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Dagostino Building Blocks, Undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Ualbany Athletics Department Holiday Cards, Undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Baseball, 0.65 cubic ft.
    - Baseball, 1966-1977 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Baseball, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Baseball, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Fall Baseball, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Baseball, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Fall Baseball, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Baseball, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Fall Baseball, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - SUNYA Baseball, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Baseball, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Fall Baseball, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Baseball, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Fall Baseball, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Baseball, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Baseball, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Baseball, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Fall Baseball, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Baseball, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Baseball, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Fall Baseball, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Baseball, Albany vs. Hartwick Program, 1992 April 23 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Baseball, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Baseball Schedule, Roster, and Article, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Baseball Rosters and Statistics, 1987-1998; 1993-1998 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Baseball Information and Statistics, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Result Forms, Baseball, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Baseball Season, 1995; 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Baseball Statistics, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Baseball, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Baseball Season, 1997; 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Baseball Season, 1998; 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Baseball Records/Statistics, 1987-1998; 1998 (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Baseball Season, 1999; 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - ECAS Division II Baseball Championship Game Box Scores, 1999 May 15 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Columbia University Baseball Media Guide, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Baseball, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Baseball, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Baseball Scorebooks, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Baseball, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Baseball Scorebook #1, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Baseball Scorebook #2, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Baseball Scorebook, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Baseball Game Programs, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Baseball Records, Coaches Records, 1958-2005; ca. 2005 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Baseball, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Baseball Records, Updated, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Baseball America Questionnaire, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - NCAA Baseball, Fayetteville Regional, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Baseball Scorebook, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Basketball, 3.95 cubic ft.
    - JV Men's Basketball Scorebooks, 1956-1961 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - JV Men's Basketball Scorebooks, 1961-1964 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - 8th Annual State University of New York Athletic Conference Basketball Tournament, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Basketball Scorebooks, 1965-1970 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Men's Basketball Statistics, 1966-2000 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Basketball Rosters and Awards, 1967-1977 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Basketball, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Basketball, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Freshmen Men's Basketball Scorebooks, 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Basketball, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Basketball, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - SUNYAC Basketball, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Basketball Pass Letters To Coaches, 1970-1974 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Basketball, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Junior Varsity Men's Basketball Scorebooks, 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - SUNYA Women's Intercollegiate Basketball, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Basketball, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Basketball, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - JV Men's Basketball Scorebook and Statistics, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Basketball, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Basketball, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - JV Men's Basketball Scorebook, Statistics, and Roster, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Basketball, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Women's Basketball Scorebooks, 1975-1980 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Basketball Albany vs. Oneonta, 1976 November 24 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Basketball Albany vs. Geneseo, 1976 December 11 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Men's J.V. Basketball Scorebook, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Basketball, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Final Varsity Basketball Statistics, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - JV Men's Basketball Scorebook and Notes, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Basketball vs. Southern Connecticut vs. Cortland, 1978 November 29; 1978 December 2; 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Basketball vs. Binghamton, Geneseo, Hartwick, 1978 December 6; 1978 December 9; 1978 December 13; 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 5)